用力夸张。自己练习这些句子，把你认为应该重读的词真正夸张出来。
Overdo it. Practice these sentences on your own, really exaggerating the word
一开始，你会觉得这样
that you think should be stressed. In the beginning, you're going to feel that this
很荒唐：没人会重读得这么狠，没人这样说话，别人会
is ridiculous. Nobody stresses this hard. Nobody talks like this. People are going
笑话我。但无论你觉得自己多用力，实际大概也只做到
to laugh at me. Yet as much as you may stress, you're probably only going to be
应有程度的一半。把这些句子打乱顺序练习
stressing about half as much as you should. Practice the sentences in random
十遍。另一个必须过度夸张的原因是，当你变得
order ten times. Another reason you must over-exaggerate is because when you get
疲惫、激动或放松时，你就会停止注意。发生这种情况时，
tired, emotional, or relaxed, you will stop paying attention. When this happens,
你会像橡皮筋一样弹回原来
like a rubber band, you're going to snap back to the way you originally were
的说话方式，也就是 10%，那只是你夸张语调的程度。
sounding, 10%, which is the extent to which you're exaggerating the intonation.
所以，如果你只把自己拉到理想位置，
So, if you just stretch yourself to the exact position where you ideally want to
一放松，几乎就会完全回到旧习惯。练习时，
be, you'll go back almost completely to the old way when you relax. For practice,
要把自己拉到远远超过正常语调范围的位置，大约 150%，这样
then, stretch yourself far beyond the normal range of intonation, 150% or so, so
当你放松时，就会回落到标准美式声音，也就是 100%。我们都会
when you relax, you relax back to a standard American sound, 100%. We all do
这样。也许这时你会想：好吧，也许你们在
it. Possibly about this time you're thinking, well, maybe you do this in
英语里会这样，但在我的语言里，我真的不觉得我们会这样。我希望你
English, but in my language, I just really don't think we do this. I'd like you to
试一个小练习。
try a little exercise.